Big problem I have with you doing sales
calls. First of all, waste of time.
Even if you're doing three a week,
that's three hours.
If I sat you in a room, this room,
locked the door, turned the camera on,
and said,
"Give me three hours of content." In a
year's time,
the compounding effect of three
hours of content or doing the sales calls,
which one do you think is going to
benefit you long term?
It's going to be the content.
Even reading books within your niche
and turning something you've learned in
the
book into a good marketing email.
There are better uses of time than selling
to
people on a one-to-one basis.
Can you imagine building a billboard
that just
advertised to one person on a farm?
It's stupid.
You put a billboard in a busy place.
We have social media.
We have so many ways to get in front of
thousands of people.
And again, if you're selling,
you're not marketing.
My next gripe is that
if you've done 20 sales calls,
which isn't a lot, you should
see the recurring themes here and go,
okay,
the prospect arrives on the call with
this insecurity, this insecurity.
They want this clarified,
and they want to understand this,
and the guarantee was
the thing that closed them.
You can build something for that.
Have you ever thought about call centers?
Call centers, they have staff
that chat to you on the phone,
and it's down to the
call center to reduce the amount of people
that actually get through to someone to
keep costs down.
Every single step you go through
is a premeditated step to reduce
your likeness of getting through.
Hey,
if you're looking to change your
insurance, go to the website.
If you're looking to do this,
then head into your local branch.
Speaking to the person
is the last ditch resort,
and it should be for you and your
sales system too.
Because it's very expensive you doing
sales calls, but not
expensive as in money,
expensive in something called opportunity
cost.
If you are giving the time for that call,
you are missing time from
something else. Right now,
I could be doing a sales call for a
high-ticket program.
Instead,
I'm making a video that's going to get me
hundreds of leads and thousands
of views.
It's the highest leverage arbitrage play
here.
But you don't always have to believe me
because I've never done a sales call in my
life.